U.S. Emergency Board No. 124 Records 5050
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Transcripts, Airline Pilots Exhibits (174), American Airline Exhibits (33), Additional Exhibits (Box 1)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Correspondence relating to the settlement of as many issues as possible previous to mediation (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Telegram to Air Line Pilots Association informing it of the commencement of mediation in New York City on October 22, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Negotiating Committee Bulletin 14 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Letters relating to the Mediation Board's suggested arbitration of the dispute and the subsequent refusal of the proposal by the disputing parties (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Letters relating to the Mediation Board's suggested arbitration of the dispute and the subsequent refusal of the proposal by the disputing parties (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Letters relating to the Mediation Board's suggested arbitration of the dispute and the subsequent refusal of the proposal by the disputing parties (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Letters relating to the Mediation Board's suggested arbitration of the dispute and the subsequent refusal of the proposal by the disputing parties (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Letters relating to the Mediation Board's suggested arbitration of the dispute and the subsequent refusal of the proposal by the disputing parties (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Letter from American Airlines to all pilots presenting a brief chronological review of the developments in the dispute, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 149)
    Covers the period between June 21, 1957 and January 3, 1958
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Telegram from the Mediation Board and affirmative reply from Air Line Pilots Association concerning further negotiations (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Telegram from the Mediation Board and affirmative reply from Air Line Pilots Association concerning further negotiations (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Further correspondence concerning extended negotiations with ultimate closing of the files by the Mediation Board (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Telegram informing parties of the creation of the Presidential Emergency Board (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Correspondence between the disputing parties concerning additional negotiating prior to the scheduled sessions with the Emergency Board (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Correspondence between the disputing parties concerning additional negotiating prior to the scheduled sessions with the Emergency Board (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Correspondence between the disputing parties concerning additional negotiating prior to the scheduled sessions with the Emergency Board (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Correspondence between the disputing parties concerning additional negotiating prior to the scheduled sessions with the Emergency Board (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Airline Pilots Exhibits - Correspondence between the disputing parties concerning additional negotiating prior to the scheduled sessions with the Emergency Board (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - "Positive Pay Plan" booklet issued by American Airlines (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Pay Formula and Rates as Proposed to Pilots, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 177)
    June 5, 1958
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Pilot proposal, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 178)
    May 9, 1958
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Pilot proposal, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 179)
    May 16, 1958
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Crew schedules effective June 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - June schedules, open for Pilot bids (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Resolution of November 1956 by both parties (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Correspondence concerning request for mediation (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Correspondence concerning request for mediation (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Correspondence concerning request for mediation (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Correspondence concerning request for mediation (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Air Line Pilots Association report to all pilots concerning Emergency Board (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Air Line Pilots Association report to all pilots concerning Emergency Board (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Bulletin from American Airlines to all Department and Division Heads concerning the company's financial condition (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Opening Remarks at Joint Conference, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 190)
    November 26, 1957
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Pay offer from American Airlines to Air Line Pilots Association, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Pay offer from American Airlines to Air Line Pilots Association, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Pay offer from American Airlines to Air Line Pilots Association, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Exchange of telegrams between disputing parties (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Exchange of telegrams between disputing parties (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Arbitration offer from Mediation Board and subsequent refusal (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Arbitration offer from Mediation Board and subsequent refusal (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Arbitration offer from Mediation Board and subsequent refusal (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Statement by American Airlines to be delivered through the mediator (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Telegram to National Mediation Board from Air Line Pilots Association informing of strike date and returns from the Mediation Board requesting further mediation (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Telegram to National Mediation Board from Air Line Pilots Association informing of strike date and returns from the Mediation Board requesting further mediation (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Telegram to National Mediation Board from Air Line Pilots Association informing of strike date and returns from the Mediation Board requesting further mediation (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Telegram to National Mediation Board from Air Line Pilots Association informing of strike date and returns from the Mediation Board requesting further mediation (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Comprehensive offer as a bargaining basis for a new agreement from American Airlines (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Pilot proposal, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 205)
    April 22, 1958
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Material relating to North Conway negotiations (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Material relating to North Conway negotiations (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - American Airlines Exhibits - Notification by the Mediation Board of the closing of its files on this case due to failure to produce a settlement (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - Additional Exhibits, J.A. Healy - Agreement between American Airlines, Incorporated and the Air Line Pilots in the service of American Airlines, Incorporated (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - Additional Exhibits, J.A. Healy - Company and Air Line Pilots Association Proposals for Change in the Current Agreement (Box 1, Folder 210)
    Part 40, Scheduled Interstate Air Carrier Certification and Operation Rules, December 31, 1955. Aeronautical Statutes and Related Material, Revised December 31, 1957, C.A.B.